fullshemaleporn.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy for fullshemaleporn.com

##### Introduction

We collect and process your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy. This policy provides you with information regarding our obligations and your rights in compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

##### Information That We Collect From You

Information that you provide to us directly might include personal information such as your name, email address and other personal details.

We may also collect non personal information that may identify you such as location, IP address, browser type, operating system and other details about the device you are using.

##### How we use your personal data

We use your personal data to process your request when you contact us by email or through our content removal form. We respect your privacy at all times. Your information will never be disclosed or shared with others without your consent, unless required to do so by law.

##### Sharing or Disclosing Your Personal Data

Whilst we will never disclose or share your data with others without your consent, we use third party processors to provide IT services; these companies will process or store your information on our behalf.

We ensure all processors acting on our behalf act in accordance with this privacy notice.

##### Your Rights

Under GDPR you have the right to access personal information that we processes about you.

You can request from us information about - 

  1. The personal data we hold about you
  2. The categories of personal data concerned
  3. The purposes of the processing
  4. Details to whom your personal data has/will be disclosed
  5. How long we retain your personal data
  6. If we did not collect the data directly from you, information about the source

You may also request from us the following-

  1. That we update any incomplete or inaccurate data about you
  2. Request that we delete your personal data in accordance with GDPR

You may request we action your rights by contacting us by email at cjtubetrader (AT) gmail.com

To ensure your data is protected, if we receive a request from you to exercise your rights, we will ask you to verify your identity before acting on the request.

##### International Transfers

Your personal data may be processed in countries outside your country of residence.

Where these transfers take place, we will ensure the same high standard of protection for your personal data at all times.

##### How Long We Retain Your Data

We only retain personal information for as long as is necessary. For further details on our data retention periods please contact us.

Where you have consented to us to use your details for direct marketing, we will keep this data until you notify us or otherwise withdraw your consent.

##### Cookies

A ‘cookie’ is a small text file sent from a website and stored on the user’s computer by the user’s web browser. Upon visiting a site that uses cookies, a cookie is downloaded onto your computer or mobile device. The next time you visit that site, your device will remember useful information such as preferences, visited pages or other options

Cookies are widely used to add functionality to websites, or to ensure they work more efficiently. Our site relies on cookies to optimise the user experience and ensure the sites services function properly.

Most web browsers allow some control to restrict or block cookies through the browser settings, however if you disable cookies you may find this affects your ability to use certain parts of our website or services. For more information about cookies please visit [https://www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/).
